https://onairrecordings.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
This statement discloses the privacy practices for the entire web site.
On Air Audio Studios Inc. may collect implicit information on an anonymous basis from users who visit this web site, for aggregate statistical analysis and site customization. Implicit information is data that can be gathered about the user without asking them. Importantly, aggregate statistical analysis means that On Air Audio Studios Inc. reviews trends based on information as a whole, but does not do so in an effort to identify the individual identity of the visitor to its site.
Any personal information that you voluntarily provide to On Air Audio Studios Inc. will be collected and used by us on an internal basis only. On Air Audio Studios Inc. does not rent or disclose any personal information about you with third parties unless you have specifically given us your consent to disclose your personal information for a designated purpose. Access to personal information is limited to On Air’s employees, contractors and agents with a need to access such information for the purposes set forth in this privacy policy. We will not use your personal information other than as set forth above without your consent.
All credit card information is not collected by On Air Audio Studios Inc., nor is it used internally or shared with any third party.
The security of your personal information is important to us. On Air Audio Studios Inc. takes technical, contractual, administrative, and physical security steps to protect personal information that you provide to us. We instruct our employees with access to your personal information that it is to be used only in adherence with the principles set forth in this Privacy Policy and the laws applicable to each specific business. In certain areas, such as when you provide credit card information to us, we work to help protect the security of your credit card information during transmission by using industry standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology.
Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses may be logged to track a user’s session. An IP address is the unique numerical identity assigned to every direct Internet access point. When an IP address is “logged”, it means that On Air’s web site associates a visit or series of visits to that unique numerical identity. On Air Audio Studios Inc. also uses cookies in order to assist in aggregate statistical analysis and sometimes provide site customization based on anonymous session tracking. In other words, On Air Audio Studios Inc. uses cookies to determine trends for users as a whole, but not as means to learn about your individual identity. Cookies, by themselves, cannot be used to determine the actual identity of users. On their own, they can be used to identify a computer, but not who is using that computer. Because of this, if On Air Audio Studios Inc. customizes the site based on cookies, we do not know who you are unless you tell us.
On Air Audio Studios Inc. collects the visitor’s domain name, referral data, as well as browser and platform type. On Air Audio Studios Inc.also counts, tracks, and aggregates the visitor’s activity into our analysis of general traffic flows at our sites. When and if On Air Audio Studios Inc. does present aggregated information to outside companies, no one would be able to identify you or contact you.
On Air Audio Studios Inc. reserves the right to change, add, or remove portions from this privacy policy at any time. However, if any change involves a plan to use your personal information in a way that differs from this privacy policy, we will first obtain your consent. When your consent is required for any action under this privacy policy, you agree that On Air Audio Studios Inc. may obtain your consent by an “opt-in” or “opt-out” method, or by other means (such as sending to you an email).
Did you know?
Music was sent down a telephone line for the first time in 1876, the year the phone was invented.
Services
Message on Hold:
How did you hear about us?
On Air Audio Studios Inc.
804c 16th Ave S.W.
.(JavaScript must be enabled to view this email address)
© Copyright 2018, On Air Audio Studios Inc.
All rights reserved
Terms of Service
Privacy Policy
